I just see
The way you’re always running from it
Hard times
The weight is floating on your stomach
High time
I checked out, where’d you go
So sly
I stay keeping my head low
I’m like uh oh
Tell that I’m okay
I’ve been spinning backwards
Don’t know who can save me
Don’t need these attachments
Baby you can’t save space
Holding onto habits
That could never save face
You’re coming for me again
Hoping to make amends
But I never knew you in the first place
Sorry I’m with my friends
What is your name again
Chances are I don’t remember your face
You called me up the other night
I kinda wish you didn’t but I know
You just really want know about us again
Us again (what’s with that?)
I’m like uh oh
Tell that I’m okay
I’ve been spinning backwards
Don’t know who can save me
Don’t need these attachments
Baby you can’t save space
Holding onto habits
That could never save face
Stay out late to party at the afters
Everyone’s so pretty on the outside
Where it matters
You can catch me swinging from the rafters
Or maybe I’ll be falling right back to you
If you catch up
You called me up the other night
I kinda wish you didn’t but I know
You just really want know about us again
Us again (what’s with that?)
I’m like uh oh
Tell that I’m okay
I’ve been spinning backwards
Don’t know who can save me
Don’t need these attachments
Baby you can’t save space
Holding onto habits
That could never save face
I’m like uh oh
Tell that I’m okay
I’ve been spinning backwards
Don’t know who can save me
Don’t need these attachments
Baby you can’t save space
Holding onto habits
That could never save face